<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<subsonic-response xmlns="http://subsonic.org/restapi" status="ok" version="1.16.1" type="ampache" serverVersion="6.6.7" openSubsonic="1">
  <podcasts>
    <channel id="600000001" url="http://rss.sciam.com/sciam/60secsciencepodcast" title="60-Second Science" description="Tune in every weekday for quick reports and commentaries on the world of science&amp;mdash;it&amp;#039;ll just take a minute" coverArt="pod-600000001" status="completed">
      <episode id="700000253" channelId="600000001" title="What The Next President Will Do about Artificial Intelligence" album="60-Second Science" description="There’s a lot of excitement and apprehension over the seemingly sudden proliferation of artificial intelligence in just about everything. Technological progress often outpaces regulation, and the next U.S. president will set the tone for AI policy. Scientific American’s associate technology editor Ben Guarino walks us through AI policies and plans from Kamala Harris and Donald Trump. Plus, we discuss the role AI generated images, videos and even voices could play in spreading misinformation around the election.&#10;&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;How the Next President Will Determine the Future of AI &#10;Lethal AI Weapons Are on the Rise. What’s Next? &#10;We Cannot Cede Control of Weapons to Artificial Intelligence &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter. &#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with associate technology editor Ben Guarino. Our show is edited by Fonda Mwangi with fact-checking by Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="1203" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-18T09:50:00+00:00" status="completed" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001" streamId="700000253" size="29287591" suffix="mp3" contentType="audio/mpeg" path="1729245000-253.mp3"/>
      <episode id="700000254" channelId="600000001" title="The Doctor Will See You, and Stop Judging You, Now" album="60-Second Science" description="How do you stop implicit bias from getting in the way of better health? This doctor wants to make learning how to manage bias as important as learning how to suture.&#10;&#10;SHOWNOTES:&#10;&#10;Have you ever felt judged at the doctor’s office, even before you said a word? Unfortunately, that’s not uncommon, and it’s often not intentional. Like everyone, doctors have unconscious biases that can affect how they treat patients, which can pose real risks to health outcomes. In this episode, host Rachel Feltman is joined by Cristina Gonzalez, a physician and professor of medicine and population health at NYU Grossman School of Medicine, to discuss how these biases form and what can be done to address them.&#10;&#10;This podcast is part of “Health Equity Heros,” an editorially independent special report that was produced with financial support from Takeda Pharmaceuticals.&#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;&#10;Discover something new everyday: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for our daily newsletter.&#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck fact-check our show. Our theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="1142" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-16T10:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000255" channelId="600000001" title="Your Rundown of the Science Nobels, and Europa Clipper Is Delayed" album="60-Second Science" description="Everything you need to know about last week’s physics, chemistry, and physiology or medicine Nobels. COVID could raise the risk of heart attacks and strokes years after original infection. Hurricane Milton causes tornadoes across Florida and delays the launch of Europa Clipper.&#10;&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;How Does Sharing a Nobel Prize Work? https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/why-chemistry-physics-and-medicine-nobel-prizes-can-be-shared-and-how-that/ &#10;Why Hurricane Milton Caused So Many Tornadoes https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/why-hurricane-milton-caused-so-many-tornadoes/ &#10;NASA’s Europa Clipper Mission Carries Special Cargo: A Poem https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/nasas-europa-clipper-mission-carries-special-cargo-a-poem/ &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter.&#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman. Our show is edited by Anaissa Ruiz Tejada with fact-checking by Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="564" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-14T09:50:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000256" channelId="600000001" title="Is Singing an Evolutionary Accident or a Critical Way to Connect?" album="60-Second Science" description="Scientific American associate news editor and music enthusiast Allison Parshall takes Science Quickly through what we know about how singing came to be. Scientists aren’t sure why humans evolved to sing, but commonalities in traditional music offer clues to how the practice evolved. Neuroscience shows us where speech and singing live in the brain and what information the forms hold. And an upcoming experiment will look into how singing might make us more connected to one another.&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;New Folk Song Analysis Finds Similarities around the World&#10;How Artificial Intelligence Helped Write This Award-Winning Song&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter.&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with guest Allison Parshall. Our show is edited by Madison Goldberg with fact-checking by Marielle Issa, Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="1526" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-11T10:25:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000257" channelId="600000001" title="The Danger of Hurricane Downpours and the End of ‘Climate Havens’" album="60-Second Science" description="Hurricanes Beryl, Francine and Helene have battered the Gulf Coast this year. Hurricane Milton is expected to add to the destruction, particularly in parts of the west coast of central Florida that are already reeling from Hurricane Helene. Scientific American’s associate editor of sustainability Andrea Thompson joins Science Quickly to help us understand how we measure hurricanes and how climate change is magnifying the damage done by these massive storms. Plus, we discuss how the catastrophic flooding in western North Carolina dispels the myth that anywhere can be a true “climate haven.”&#10;&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;New Hurricane Forecasts Could Predict Terrifying Explosive Intensification https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/new-hurricane-forecasts-could-predict-terrifying-explosive-intensification/ &#10;Hurricanes Kill People for Years after the Initial Disaster  https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/hurricanes-kill-people-for-years-after-the-initial-disaster/ &#10;Hurricane Helene Signals the End of the ‘Climate Haven’ https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/hurricane-helene-signals-the-end-of-the-climate-haven/ &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter.&#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with guest Andrea Thompson, Scientific American’s associate editor of sustainability. Our show is edited by Fonda Mwangi with fact-checking by Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith. &#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="975" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-09T09:50:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000258" channelId="600000001" title="Stem Cell Treatments for Diabetes and a Dolphin’s Smile" album="60-Second Science" description="Hurricane Helene’s death toll continues to rise. Marburg virus is spreading in Rwanda, but risks for a global outbreak are low. Researchers in Beijing used stem cell treatments to reverse diabetes in a patient. Plus, we discuss a map of a fruit fly’s brain and dolphin smiles.&#10;&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;Hurricanes Kill People for Years after the Initial Disaster https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/hurricanes-kill-people-for-years-after-the-initial-disaster/ &#10;See an Amazingly Detailed Map of the Fruit Fly Brain&#10;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/see-an-amazingly-detailed-map-of-the-fruit-fly-brain/ &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter.&#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman. Our show is edited by Anaissa Ruiz Tejada with fact-checking by Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck.  The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="595" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-07T09:50:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000259" channelId="600000001" title="The Hidden Secrets of Math: Uncharted Territory (Part 3)" album="60-Second Science" description="Drag queen and mathematics communicator Kyne Santos tells us the questions that modern mathematicians are grappling with, from infinite tiling to the structure of math itself.&#10;We hope you enjoyed the final episode of this Friday miniseries about magical math. You can listen to parts one and two wherever you get your podcasts or at the links below. &#10;Recommended reading:&#10;– Discover Math’s Elegance and Power with Drag Queen Kyne Santos&#10;– Is Math Part of Nature or an Invention of the Mind?&#10;– Inside Mathematicians’ Search for the Mysterious ‘Einstein Tile’&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter. &#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with guest Kyne Santos. Our show is edited by Madison Goldberg with fact-checking by Shayna Posses, Emily Makowski and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="1044" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-04T10:25:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000260" channelId="600000001" title="Your Next Pain Prescription Could Come without Addiction Risk" album="60-Second Science" description="The Food and Drug Administration has granted priority review to suzetrigine, a novel painkiller. It’s part of a new class of medications that could provide relief to those with chronic pain. The drugs target sodium channels on nerve cells, stopping pain signaling at the periphery. Journalist Marla Broadfoot explains the biology of aches and pains and the reasons it is so challenging to develop well-tolerated medications for pain.&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;New Painkiller Could Bring Relief to Millions—Without Addiction Risk &#10;Ozempic Quiets Food Noise in the Brain—But How? &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter. &#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with guest Marla Broadfoot. Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck fact-check our show. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="733" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-10-02T09:50:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000261" channelId="600000001" title="Fighting Global Misinformation, Ditching Plastic Bottles, and Hunting with an Octopus" album="60-Second Science" description="From the United Nations General Assembly, host Rachel Feltman interviews Melissa Fleming, the U.N.’s undersecretary-general for global communications, on how misinformation and distrust in science are impacting global well-being. Plus, we note caveats to a major social media study and explain how food packaging can be harmful to the environment and human health.&#10;&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;Why It’s So Hard to Recycle Plastic https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/why-its-so-hard-to-recycle-plastic/ &#10;How Deadly Is Mpox, What Vaccines Are Effective, and Other Questions Answered https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/how-deadly-is-mpox-what-vaccines-are-effective-and-other-questions-answered/ &#10;61 Unexpected ‘Forever Chemicals’ Found in Food Packaging https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/61-unexpected-pfas-forever-chemicals-found-in-food-packaging/ &#10;&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter. &#10;&#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio.  This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman with guest Melissa Fleming, undersecretary-general for global communications at the United Nations. Our show is edited by Anaissa Ruiz Tejada with fact-checking by Shayna Posses and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="866" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-09-30T10:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
      <episode id="700000262" channelId="600000001" title="The Hidden Secrets of Math: Invented or Discovered? (Part 2)" album="60-Second Science" description="Where does math come from? Mathematicians are still debating whether math is an inherent part of nature or an invention of the human mind. Mathematics communicator and drag queen Kyne will guide you through the question of what math really is in this three-part Friday miniseries.&#10;Recommended reading:&#10;– Gift Wrapping Five Oranges Has Outwitted the Best Minds in Mathematics for Generations &#10;– The SAT Problem That Everybody Got Wrong&#10;E-mail us at sciencequickly@sciam.com if you have any questions, comments or ideas for stories we should cover!&#10;Discover something new every day: subscribe to Scientific American and sign up for Today in Science, our daily newsletter. &#10;Science Quickly is produced by Rachel Feltman, Fonda Mwangi, Kelso Harper, Madison Goldberg and Jeff DelViscio. This episode was hosted by Rachel Feltman and Kyne Santos. Our show is edited by Madison Goldberg with fact-checking by Shayna Posses, Emily Makowski and Aaron Shattuck. The theme music was composed by Dominic Smith.&#10;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices" duration="808" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-09-27T09:50:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000001" coverArt="600000001"/>
    </channel>
    <channel id="600000002" url="https://anchor.fm/s/90932e8/podcast/rss" title="Plays Well with Others" description="From Creative Commons, a podcast about the art and science of collaboration. With a focus on the tools, techniques, and mechanics of collaboration, we explore how today&amp;#039;s most interesting collaborators are making new things, solving old problems, and getting things done &amp;mdash; together. Hosted by Creative Commons CEO Ryan Merkley. " coverArt="pod-600000002" status="completed">
      <episode id="700000022" channelId="600000002" title="What Do an Army of Ants and an Online Encyclopedia Have in Common?" album="Plays Well with Others" description="&lt;p&gt;“Stigmergy is a mechanism of indirect coordination, through the environment, between agents or actions,” &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stigmergy&amp;quot;&gt;according to Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;. “The principle is that the trace left in the environment by an action stimulates the performance of a next action, by the same or a different agent.” Wikipedia should know all about stigmergy, since it’s almost a perfect description of how Wikipedia itself is made. While this model of collaboration is most commonly associated with ants, not global knowledge sharing, we’ll explore both and how they’ve shaped our world through asynchronous collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Join us as we talk to Katherine Maher, the executive director of the Wikimedia Foundation (the nonprofit organization that runs Wikipedia), and Clint Penick, an ant researcher and assistant research professor in the Biomimicry Center at Arizona State University.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;All original content in Plays Well with Others is available under a &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&amp;quot;&gt;Creative Commons BY license&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;This episode contains music by &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.sessions.blue/&amp;quot;&gt;Blue Dot Sessions&lt;/a&gt;, available under a &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&amp;quot;&gt;Creative Commons BY-NC license&lt;/a&gt; at the &lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://freemusicarchive.org/music/Blue_Dot_Sessions/&amp;quot;&gt;Free Music Archive&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;We also use sound effects, available under CC licenses and in the public domain, from &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://freesound.org/&amp;quot;&gt;Freesound&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;For links to these tracks and for more information about our show, please visit &lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://playswellwithothers.org/&amp;quot;&gt;playswellwithothers.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" duration="1400" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2019-03-28T07:00:00+00:00" status="completed" parent="600000002" coverArt="600000002" streamId="700000022" size="22657395" suffix="m4a" contentType="audio/mp4" path="1553756400-What Do an Army of Ants and an Online Encyclopedia Have in Common_-https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2020-02-15%2F490c1c2b3a8e1c50636c61e5fb8505c4.m4a"/>
      <episode id="700000023" channelId="600000002" title="I Laughed So Hard I Cried" album="Plays Well with Others" description="&lt;p&gt;On our first episode, we look at how collaboration happens in one of comedy&amp;#039;s most storied (and tough) environments — the TV writers&amp;#039; room. It&amp;#039;s where the magic happens, but it can also be one of the most brutally competitive places a creative person will ever work. We talk to two writer-comedians, Anne Lane and Wayne Federman, about their experiences working in writers&amp;#039; rooms on shows like &lt;em&gt;Rick and Morty&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Late Night with Jimmy Fallon&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;All original content in &lt;em&gt;Plays Well with Others&lt;/em&gt; is available under a &lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&amp;quot;&gt;Creative Commons BY license&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" duration="1195" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2019-02-19T05:44:17+00:00" status="completed" parent="600000002" coverArt="600000002" streamId="700000023" size="19328679" suffix="m4a" contentType="audio/mp4" path="1550555057-I Laughed So Hard I Cried-https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2020-02-14%2F71cdb1450b1899304a5828d35dd982f4.m4a"/>
      <episode id="700000024" channelId="600000002" title="Coming Soon" album="Plays Well with Others" description="&lt;p&gt;From Creative Commons, a new podcast about the art and science of collaboration. With a focus on the tools, techniques, and mechanics of collaboration, we’re going to explore how today&amp;#039;s most interesting collaborators are making new things, solving old problems, and getting things done — together. Hosted by Creative Commons CEO Ryan Merkley. Premieres Tuesday, February 19.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;" duration="1401" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2019-02-06T21:33:45+00:00" status="completed" parent="600000002" coverArt="600000002" streamId="700000024" size="1848102" suffix="mp3" contentType="audio/mpeg" path="1549488825-Coming Soon-https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F2019-1-6%2F9620141-48000-2-444b85150cc4a.mp3"/>
    </channel>
    <channel id="600000012" url="https://www.abc.net.au/radio/programs/trace/feed/8597522/podcast.xml" title="Trace" description="An investigative podcast hosted by ABC journalist Rachael Brown, Trace examines the fractures in Australia&amp;#039;s criminal justice system, and the decades-long ripples they have caused." status="completed">
      <episode id="700001937" channelId="600000012" title="S1 BONUS | A million-dollar reward" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Victoria Police is set to announce a one million dollar reward for information that finally solves the case of Maria James, who was murdered in the back of her bookshop 44 years ago. And for the first time in seven years of investigating this case, police grant an interview to Rachael Brown.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="936" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2024-06-13T17:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001938" channelId="600000012" title="S1 Bonus | Maria James inquest finding" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;A Victorian Coroner has failed to name a killer in the 1980 cold case of Maria James. Her sons are devastated. But there&amp;#039;s still hope, in leads yet to be chased by police.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1114" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2022-04-01T02:30:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001939" channelId="600000012" title="S1 Bonus | The Inquest" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;The new coronial inquest into the murder of Maria James has wrapped up. Will the Coroner be able to name her killer? And of the police exhibits that haven&amp;#039;t disappeared, what DNA testing can be done? This episode nears us closer to the end of the James brothers&amp;#039; 41-year-fight for answers for their mum.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="3927" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2021-11-03T14:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001940" channelId="600000012" title="S1 Bonus | Breakthrough in Maria James cold case" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;The discovery of a police exhibit - thought to be missing for around three decades - could finally help unmask the killer in the 1980 cold case of Maria James.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1605" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2021-08-12T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001941" channelId="600000012" title="S2 BONUS — The Price" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;The Royal Commission has released its final report into defence lawyer turned police informer Nicola Gobbo.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2453" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-12-16T14:01:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001942" channelId="600000012" title="S2 08 | End game" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;We reveal the story of Nicola Gobbo&amp;#039;s audacious bid to return to Australia.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2542" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-09-21T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001943" channelId="600000012" title="S2 07 | Reckoning" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Everything unravels, for Nicola Gobbo and Victoria Police. Their secret is out.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2435" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-09-14T15:01:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001944" channelId="600000012" title="S2 06 | Whatever it takes" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Nicola hits rock bottom, but Victoria Police wants her to take on a new role ... as a witness.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2458" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-09-07T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001945" channelId="600000012" title="S2 05 | Glittering prize" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Nicola wants to be the best source ever, and she leads police to the biggest target of all: the mafia. Her double life is getting riskier, but she can&amp;#039;t stop. This episode charts an addiction and a crash.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2377" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-08-31T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001946" channelId="600000012" title="S2 04 | Rubicon" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Nicola crosses the point of no return and becomes a police informer. She&amp;#039;ll represent clients, while passing on the underworld&amp;#039;s secrets to Victoria Police.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2267" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-08-24T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001947" channelId="600000012" title="S2 03 | The darkest night" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;A drug house burglary smells of police corruption and a police informer is executed.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2379" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-08-17T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001948" channelId="600000012" title="S2 02 | One of the crew" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;As the gangland war explodes, both police and criminals start questioning Nicola&amp;#039;s allegiances. Where do her loyalties lie?&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2257" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-08-10T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001949" channelId="600000012" title="S2 01 | Nicola" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;We meet Nicola Gobbo in a secret location, in hiding, now that her double life as a police informer is out, and she begins telling us her full story.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2143" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-08-03T17:30:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001950" channelId="600000012" title="INTRODUCING Trace season 2 - The Informer" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Lawyer Nicola Gobbo represented some of Australia&amp;#039;s most dangerous criminals, all the while secretly working as a police informer. Why did she do it?&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="313" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2020-07-27T15:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001951" channelId="600000012" title="S1 07 | Hope" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;More than a year on from their plea for a new coronial inquest, the James brothers get a decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will they finally get answers to the burning questions they&amp;#039;ve carried for 38 years about the murder of their mother?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what about those items Trace has been given that might have DNA on them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can they identify the killer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We take them to one of the world&amp;#039;s best DNA labs, with some of the most sensitive equipment, to find out.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2217" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2018-12-03T16:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001952" channelId="600000012" title="S1 06 | Limbo" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;New evidence has been found. So can police test it for a trace of the killer? What happened to crucial documents? And a new confession.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is nearly a year since the James brothers applied for a new coronial inquest into their mum&amp;#039;s murder, but the case hangs in legal limbo. &lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1752" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2018-06-12T18:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001953" channelId="600000012" title="S1 05 | Wait" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;The fall-out from major revelations in the Maria James cold-case continue, as her sons make a desperate plea to the Coroner. &lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1458" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-09-06T16:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001954" channelId="600000012" title="S1 04 | DNA" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;There&amp;#039;s a major break in the case, as Trace uncovers a police bungle in the murder of Maria James. But it only serves to throw up more questions than answers, as the James brothers continue their desperate search for justice.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2040" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-07-12T07:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001955" channelId="600000012" title="S1 03 | Sins" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;A second person of interest emerges within the church. Rachael Brown investigates their past and discovers a dark and disturbing history. &lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1674" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-07-05T12:30:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001956" channelId="600000012" title="BONUS | How your leads are helping the investigation" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Since Trace was first released, the ABC has received over 50 emails from the community with leads and tip offs. In this bonus update, reporter Rachael Brown follows up with two women who got in touch to say they saw men acting suspiciously around Maria&amp;#039;s bookshop at the time of her murder. Send us your tips: &lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:trace@abc.net.au&amp;quot;&gt;trace@abc.net.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="465" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-07-04T05:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001957" channelId="600000012" title="S1 02 | Confessions" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;Rachael Brown&amp;#039;s investigation into the death of Maria James turns to the local Church, and Rachael tracks down a new witness who saw someone covered in blood around the time of Maria&amp;#039;s death.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="2140" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-06-27T16:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001958" channelId="600000012" title="S1 01 | Bookshop murder" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;On a winter morning in June 1980, Maria James turned to her son Mark and looked him in the eyes. &amp;quot;If anything happens to me, look after your brother.&amp;quot; Later that day she was found stabbed to death at the back of her suburban Melbourne bookshop. &lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="1823" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-06-20T20:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
      <episode id="700001959" channelId="600000012" title="INTRODUCING: Trace, series 1 — Bookshop Murder" album="Trace" description="&#10;                 &lt;p&gt;June, 1980, suburban Melbourne: Mother of two Maria James is stabbed to death in the back of her bookshop. Her killer has never been found. Was it a scorned lover? A random stranger? Or was Maria&amp;#039;s murder tied up in the sins of the Catholic Church?&lt;/p&gt; &#10;            " duration="115" genre="Podcast" isDir="false" publishDate="2017-06-16T23:00:00+00:00" status="pending" parent="600000012"/>
    </channel>
  </podcasts>
</subsonic-response>
